Franz Waxman Papers
Franz Waxman Papers
- Recordings
  - Professional recordings
    - Bride of Frankenstein (3 of 4), waxman_0896; part of Franz Waxman re-recording preservation project 1979. Preservation re-recording of Bride of Frankenstein soundtrack by Franz Waxman for Universal Pictures platic pressing 33 1/3 rpm. Menuetto pre-eq; Danse Macabre 729-819 T-2, t-3, t-4. Re-recorded 3/20/79; this copy 1/23/80; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Menuetto; Danse macabre
    - Bride of Frankenstein (4 of 4), waxman_0897; part of Franz Waxman re-recording preservation project 1979. Preservation re-recording of Bride of Frankenstein sound track by Franz Waxman for Universal Pictures platic pressing 33 1/3 cellutone acetate. re-recorded 3/29/79 this copy 1/23/80.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      [no title listed]
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (1 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0494; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      Creation 1. Part
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (2 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0495; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      II. Part Creation Scene
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (3 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0496; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      III. Part Creation Scene
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (4 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0497; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      Monster Entrance, Side A; N.G., Side A; Pastorale and Chase, Side A
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (5 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0498; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      Menuetto, Side A
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (6 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0499; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      N.G. Side A; Without Bones, Side A; With Bones, Side A
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (7 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0500; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      Creation Side A
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (8 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0501; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      N.G., Side A; Creation II Part, Side A
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (9 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0502; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      Creation III Part, Side A
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (10 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0503; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (11 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0504; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      Monster Entrance, Side A; N.G., Side A; Pastorale, Side A
    - Bride Of Frankenstein (12 of 12), 04/03/1935; waxman_0505; Live Stage 10; VinylDisc
      N.G., Side A; Without B., Side A; With B., Side A
    - Burmese Folk and Traditional Music, 1953; waxman_0751; Burmese Folk Music; Contains Insert; VinylDisc
      Side 1 Kyo Song; Byaw Than; Patt Waing; Maung Saing; Saing; Saung; Pattala; Side 2 Don Min; Si Daw; Bon Gyi Than; Do Butt; O Zi; Kar Gyin; Burmese Violin; Burmese Guitar; Burmese Piano
    - But For You, waxman_0589; Shellac disc
      But For You, Side A; There's Magic In The Air, Side B
    - Butterfly = madam, waxman_0826; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Buy A Ford, waxman_0810; Automobile Commercials; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Buy A Ford
    - By the Waters of Minnetonka, waxman_0280; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      By the Waters of Minnetonka, Side A; Winnebego Love Song, Side B; Love with Tears, Side B; Pueblo Lullaby, Side B; Omaha Ceremonial, Side B
    - By The Weeping Waters, waxman_0283; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      By The Weeping Waters, Side A; Aooah, Side B; Her Blanket, Side B
    - C'est Pour Ca Qu'on S'aime, waxman_0256; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      C'est Pour Ca Qu'on S'aime, Side A; L'autre, Side B
    - C'est Pour Ca Qu'on S'aime, waxman_0259; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Cantata No. 4, waxman_0633; Shellac disc
      Sinfonia, Side A; Chorus: Versus I, Side A; Duet Versus 6, Side B; Chorale: versus 7, Side B
    - Cantata No. 4, waxman_0634; Shellac disc
      Chorus: Versus 1 Christ Lag in Todesbanden (concluded), Side A; Aria: Versus 5 Hier ist das rechte Osterlamm, Side B
    - Cantata No. 4, waxman_0635; Shellac disc
      Duet: Versus 2 Den Tod niemand zwingen kunnt' (Part 1), Side A; Chorus: Versus 4 Es war ein wunderlicher Krieg, Side B
    - Cantata No. 4, waxman_0636; Shellac disc
      Duet: Versus 2 Den Tod niemand zwingen kunnt'(concluded), Side A; Aria: Versus 3 Jesus Christus, Gottes Sohn, Side B
    - Canticum Sacrum, 06/17/1957; waxman_0999; 1/4 inch audio tape; running time 31:00 (Oversize 121)
      Greetings Prelude; Symphonies of Wind Instruments; Canticum Sacrum
    - Caprice, waxman_0595; Shellac disc
      Caprice
    - Carmen, waxman_0253; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Vorspiel
    - Carmen Fantasy, waxman_0918; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
    - Carmen Fantasy Side 1, 9/9/1946; waxman_0128; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Carmen Fantasy Side 2, 9/9/1946; waxman_0129; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Carousel - Waltz, waxman_0378; Commercial, 78rpm; Shellac disc
    - Carousel: Soliloquy, waxman_0349; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      I wonder what he'll think of me, Side A; I can see him when he's seventeen, Side B
    - Casablanca: Classic Film Scores for Humphrey Bogart, 1974; waxman_0748; Contains Insert; VinylDisc
      Side A Casablanca Main Title; The immigrants; Morocco; "Sam I thought I told you never to play"; As time Goes By; Flashback; Rick Remembers Paris; Love Scene; The Airport; Major Strasser's Death; "...the beginning of a beautiful friendship"; Parrage to Marseille Rescue At Sea; The Treasure of the Sierra Madre Main Title; The Trek to the Gold; Fool's Gold; the Letter; Finale; The Gold Scatters in the Wind; The Big Sleep Love Themes; The Caine Mutiny March; Side B To Have and Have Not Main Title; The Two Mrs. Carrolls Main Title; The Embrace; The Storm; The Poisoned Milk; The Window; Geoffrey's Madness; Finale; Sabrina Main Title; The Larrabee Estate; The Left Hand of God Love Theme; Sahara Main Title; Virginia City Stagecoach; Love Scene; Key Largo Main Title; The Bridge; McCloud and Mr. Temple; Reminiscence; Morning; Finale
    - Cello Concerto in A minor, Opus 129, waxman_0985; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
    - Cello Concerto in A minor, Opus 129, waxman_0981; A Track, beginning, cadenza, from V to end; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
    - Chamber Music Concert, 12/28/1951; waxman_0988; County Museum (Los Angeles?); 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
    - Chansons: Meisenbruch, Mummer, Ich hab die Sonne am Morgen, Wenn man wieder am Ende steht, Keiner auf der Welt, Mein Mann ist verhindent, Ich versetze Berge, He l'Amour, Das Lied vom kleinen Wind, Ponny, Let's Do It, waxman_0962; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Chant of the Eagle Dance, waxman_0278; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Chant of the Eagle Dance, Side A; Chant of the Snake Dance, Side B
    - Charles Coiner United Nations Address, 1/2/1953; waxman_0020; address by Charles Coiner to United Nations; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Charles Coiner United Nations Address, 1/2/1953; waxman_0021; address by Charles Coiner to United Nations; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Children's Corner, waxman_0267; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Doctor Gradus and Parnassum, Side A; Jumbo's Lullaby, Side B
    - Children's Corner, waxman_0268; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Serenade for the Doll, Side A; The Snow is Dancing, Side B
    - Childrens' Corner, parts 5 and 6, waxman_0269; Shellac disc
      Childrens' Corner, parts 5 and 6
    - Choir With Orchestra, waxman_0803; Includes business card: Themes & Variations, Inc., John W. Waxman, president, with a note: "Bill - for the archiver!"; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 133)
      Choir With Orchestra
    - Chopin Concerto, 02/11/1946; waxman_0033; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Chopin Concerto, 02/11/1946; waxman_0034; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Chorale-Prelude-Jesu, waxman_0330; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Chorale-Prelude-Jesu, Side A; Joy of Man's Desiring, Side A; Prelude in E Major, Side B
    - Chorale and Canonic Variations Conclusion, waxman_1022; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Christmas Carol (KFI), 12/26/1943; waxman_0106; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Circus Overture; Para el Payaso, waxman_1046; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Clair De Lune, waxman_0277; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      No 3 Suite Bergamasque
    - Clair De Lune, waxman_0597; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Clair De Lune, Side A; Golliwog's Cake-Walk, Side B
    - [Classical compositions, various], 06/11/1956; waxman_1001; 10th anniversary performance.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 121)
      Academic Festival Overture; Opus 80; Symphony in D; Concerto for Violin and Orchestra; Sinfonietta for String Orchestra and Timpany; The Pines of Rome
    - Classic Film Scores for Bette Davis, 1973; waxman_0747; includes insert; VinylDisc
      Side A Now Voyager; Dark Victory; A Stolen Life; The Private Lives of Elizabeth and Essex; Mr. Skeffington; In This Our Life; Side B All About Eve; Jezebel; Beyond the Forest; Juarez; The Letter; All This and Heaven Too
    - Classical Symphony, waxman_1087; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Classical Symphony in D Major, waxman_0345; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Side A 4th Movement - Finale - Molto Vivace; Side B The Love for Three Oranges
    - Columbia Presents Corwin (Side 2 of 3), 7/10/1945; waxman_0223; film score; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Columbia Presents Corwin (Sides 1 and 3 of 3), 7/10/1945; waxman_0222; film score; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Comedy Sketch, waxman_0805; Home Recording; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Comedy Sketch - "In an Office"; Piano Elude
    - Re-recordings of commercial discs (1 of 4), waxman_0905; part of Franz Waxman re-recording preservation project. Preservation re-recordings of Telefuken a 1484 45 rpm; Echo 113 78rpm; Electrola EG 2639 78rpm; German Grammophon 24764B 78rpm; ABC paramount 45-10196 45rpm; Italian Columbia SCMQ 1099 45rpm; Columbia Promotion record 4-41024 45rpm; Columbia 4-42513 radio station copy 45rpm.Re-recorded by Walter welch December 7, 1970.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
      Gruss Und Kuss Veronika; coning in time; Scampolo: Furn Groschen Liebe; Cimarron; Sayonara; Fior di Loto, katsumi Love theme; Syaronara, katsumi love theme,; my Geisha, you are sympathy to me.
    - Re-recordings of commercial discs (2 of 4), waxman_0906; part of Franz Waxman re-recording preservation project. Preservation re-recordings of commercial 78 rpms; French gramophone K-7938; French Gramophome K-6652 special edition; Odeon 0-11779a; Decca PO 5107 Polydor; Decca PO 5107 polydor; Parlophone R 1557; Parlophone B 48249-I; Parlophone B 48248-II. Re-recorded by Walter Welch December 7, 1970; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
      Plus seule chaque Jour; Le Petite de Montparnasse; Ich und die Laisern; the slump is over; without a word; the slump os over one only sees that in Paris; the only girl, ther's magic in the air; paprika; Scampolo
    - Re-recordings of commercial discs (3 of 4), waxman_0907; part of Franz Waxman re-recording preservation project. Preservation re-recordings of commercial 78 rpm recordings/ Columbia DW2169; Columbia DW 2145; victor 25475; Kristall 3356; Odeon )-11827; Parlophon 48248; Gloria GO 10424; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
      Mir ist so millionar zu mute: Scampolo Furn Groschen Liebe; Scampolo ach, wie ist das leven schon; Paparika das Gluck kommt nur einmal im Leben: paprika ach, wie oft kommt die Liebe unverfofft; Love on the run gone; Gruss und Kuss Veroniks
    - Re-recordings of commercial discs (4 of 4), waxman_0908; part of Franz Waxman re-recording preservation project. Preservation re-recordings of Decca 1098; Capitol 142; Brunswick 7793; Columbia DW 2173; Columbia DF 1576 Cl 5005; CL 5009, CL 5008. Re-recorded by Walter L. Welch December 3, 1970.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
      Love on the run: gone; Old acquaintance; Love on the rund: Gone; Gruss und Kuss Veronika: die Kleinen Madchen mit d. treuen blick; La Crise est Finie: onne voit ca qua Paris, Sana un mot.
    - Concert Symphony for Violin and Orchestra, waxman_0742; VinylDisc
      Side 1 Allegro con Brio; Adagio; Adagio; Side 2 Lento
    - Concert Waltz; Façade, waxman_0861; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 116)
    - Concertante, waxman_0885; part of Franz Waxman re-recording project 1979. Preservation re-recording of Universal records acetate 78 rpm. Re-recording by Syracuse University Audio Archives.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Concertante
    - Concertino Da Camera, waxman_0332; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Concertino Da Camera, Side A; Rhapsody for Alto Saxophone, Side B
    - Concertino Da Camera, waxman_0333; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Concertino Da Camera
    - Concertino da Camera, waxman_1065; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto, aired 07/08/1957; waxman_0413; Los Angeles Festival Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Le Martyr (start), side A; Le Martyr (continued), side B
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra, waxman_0334; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Concerto for Piano and Orchestra
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra, waxman_0335; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra, waxman_0336; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Concerto for Piano and Orchestra No. 2, waxman_1052; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Concerto for Two Pianos, waxman_0952; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 119)
    - Concerto for Two Violins and Orchestra, waxman_1041; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Concerto for Violin, waxman_0657; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Concerto For Violin, 2nd Movement, Part 1, Side A; Concerto For Violin, 4th Movement, Side B
    - Concerto For Violin, 06/23/1946; waxman_0656; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Concerto for Violin, 1st Movement, Part 1, Side A; Concerto for Violin, 2nd Movement, Concluded, Side B; 3rd Movement, Side B
    - Concerto For Violin and Orchestra, waxman_1073; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto For Violin and Orchestra, waxman_1078; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 1 (1 of 2), waxman_1063; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 1 (2 of 2), waxman_1064; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 2 in G Minor, waxman_0337; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      1st Movement - Allegro Moderato
    - Concerto No. 2, Konzert Music (1 of 2), waxman_1088; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 2, Konzert Music (2 of 2), waxman_1089; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 23 in A Major, waxman_1036; 1/4 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 3 (1 of 2), waxman_1090; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 3 (2 of 2), waxman_1091; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 4 (1 of 2), waxman_1061; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 4 (2 of 2), waxman_1062; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 5 (1 of 2), waxman_1092; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto No. 5 (2 of 2), waxman_1093; 1/2 inch audio tape
    - Concerto Symphonique No. 4, waxman_0313; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Concerto Symphonique No. 4
    - Coriolan Overture Op. 62, waxman_0347; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Coriolan Overture; Eroica Symphony, 06/27/1946; waxman_0026; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Costa Brava, waxman_0756; Main Theme from the Motion Picture "Sayonara"; film soundtrack; instrumental; VinylDisc; running time 2:12; 2:25
      Costa Brava, side A; Katsumi Love Theme, side B
    - [Crime in the streets], waxman_0879; part of Franz Waxman re-recording project 1979. Preservation re-recordings of Lindbrook Production Readi Recorders and Decca. Re-recorded by Walter Welch December 10, 1970.; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
      Crime in the streets: background music par II; theme and variations- fugato.
    - Crime In The Streets, waxman_0436; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Background Music, Side A
    - Crime In The Streets, waxman_0437; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Crime in the Streets (1 of 3), waxman_0933; Reel 1 of 3; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
    - Crime in the Streets (2 of 3), waxman_0934; Reel 2 of 3; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
    - Crime in the Streets (3 of 3), waxman_0935; Reel 3 of 3; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 118)
    - Crosby Williams Christmas tv shows 1971, waxman_0900; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
    - Cydalise Et Le Chevre-pied, waxman_0326; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Cydalise Et Le Chevre-pied
    - Damnation of Faust, waxman_0620; Shellac disc
      Rakoczy March, Side A; Presto and March, Side B
    - Dance Song, waxman_0279; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Dance Song; Butterfly Dance, Side A; Shuffling Feet, Side A; Deer Dance, Side B
    - Dark World, 11/7/1940; waxman_0226; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Darling, How I Long To Go, waxman_0809; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Darling, How I Long To Go; Where the Lonesome Pine Trees Blow
    - Das Currendemadchen, waxman_0308; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Das Currendemadchen, Side A; O Mond, Side B
    - Das Deutsche Volkslied, waxman_0247; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      "Ah, how then is it possible", Side A; "Thou who art in my thoughts", Side B
    - Das Deutsche Volkslied, waxman_0248; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      "The good Comrade - I had a Comrade", Side A; "Hunter's Life - In Wood and on Moorland", Side B
    - Das gluck kommt nur einmal im Leben, waxman_0586; Shellac disc
      Das Gluck kommt nur einmal im Leben, Side A; 1000 Worte Liebe, Side B
    - Dause Macabre, 01/08/1938; waxman_0712; Shellac disc
      Dause Macabre, Side A; La Mer, Side B
    - Day At The Circus, 09/19/1939; waxman_0796; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Tiger Rag
    - Death and Transfiguration, parts 1 and 3, waxman_0485; performance recording (2; 4).; Lacquer discs/acetates (Oversize 133)
    - Death and Transfiguration (2 of 3), waxman_0486; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 4, Side A; Symphony No. 4 Part 1, Side B
    - Death and Transfiguration (3 of 3), waxman_0487; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Part 5, Side A; Symphony No. 4 Part 2, Side B
    - Debussy Saint-Sebastien, waxman_1105; part of Franz Waxman re-recording project 1979 [Franz Waxman Re-Recording Project (3 of 3)]; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 120)
      Le Martye de Saint-Sebastien (conclusion)
    - Dedication, waxman_0244; Shellac disc
      Widmung "Dedication"; "In the Shadow of My Locks"; "Mouse-trap Spell"
    - Democratic Program (Sides 1 and 3), 11/06/1944; waxman_0241; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Democratic Program (Sides 2 and 4), 11/06/1944; waxman_0240; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - Der Freischutz (1 of 2), waxman_0384; commercial, 78rpm; opera; Shellac disc
      In 3 Parts, Part III, Overture - Completion, side A; Intermezzo to Act III, side B
    - Der Freischutz (2 of 2), waxman_0385; commercial, 78rpm; opera; Imported Recording; Shellac disc
      In 3 Parts, Overture - First Part, side A; Overture - Second Part, side B
    - Der Rosenkavalier (1 of 4), aired 10/08/1946; waxman_0156; concert broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, Act 2, part 1; side B, Act 2, part 3
    - Der Rosenkavalier (1 of 8), aired 12/14/1946; waxman_0140; Concert Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, part 1; side B, part 2
    - Der Rosenkavalier (2 of 4), aired 10/08/1946; waxman_0157; concert broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, Act 2, part 2; side B, Act 2, part 4
    - Der Rosenkavalier (2 of 8), aired 12/14/1946; waxman_0141; Concert Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, part 3; side B, part 4
    - Der Rosenkavalier (3 of 4), aired 10/08/1946; waxman_0158; concert broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, track 1, Act 2, part 5; track 2, Act 3, part 1; side B, Act 3, part 3
    - Der Rosenkavalier (3 of 8), aired 12/14/1946; waxman_0142; Concert Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, part 5; side B, part 7
    - Der Rosenkavalier (4 of 4), aired 10/08/1946; waxman_0159; concert broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, Act 3, part 2; side B, Act 3, part 4
    - Der Rosenkavalier (4 of 8), aired 12/14/1946; waxman_0143; Concert Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, part 6; side B, part 8
    - Der Rosenkavalier (5 of 8), aired 12/14/1946; waxman_0144; Concert Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, part 10; side B, part 12
    - Der Rosenkavalier (6 of 8), aired 12/14/1946; waxman_0145; Concert Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, part 9; side B, part 11
    - Der Rosenkavalier (7 of 8), aired 12/14/1946; waxman_0146; Concert Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, part 13; side B, part 15
    - Der Rosenkavalier (8 of 8), aired 12/14/1946; waxman_0147; Concert Broadcast; Lacquer discs/acetates
      side A, part 14
    - The Devil Doll (1 of 9), waxman_0506; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Devil Doll (2 of 9), waxman_0507; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Devil Doll (3 of 9), waxman_0508; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Devil Doll (4 of 9), waxman_0509; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Devil Doll (5 of 9), waxman_0510; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Devil Doll (6 of 9), waxman_0511; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Devil Doll (7 of 9), waxman_0512; Lacquer discs/acetates
    - The Devil Doll (8 of 9), waxman_0513; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Lashna
    - The Devil Doll (9 of 9), waxman_0514; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Bying flowers - Accordion Solo
    - Dialogues for Jazz Combo and Orchestra, waxman_0684; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Dialogues for Jazz Combo and Orchestra
    - Dialogues for Jazz Combo and Symphony Orchestra, Movements 3 and 4, waxman_0868; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 117)
    - Diamond Jim Brady, waxman_0524; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Lullaby
    - Diamond Jim Brady, waxman_0525; Lacquer discs/acetates
      After The Banquet
    - Diamond Jim Brady, waxman_0526; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Jim Brady's End
    - Die Flederamaus Overture, waxman_0344; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
    - Die Hochzeit des Figaro, waxman_0389; Commercial 78 rpm; Shellac disc
      Die Hochzeit des Figaro, Side A; Die Entfuhrung aus dem Serail, Side B
    - Die kleinen Madchen mit d.treuen Blick, waxman_0582; Shellac disc
      Die kleinen Madchen mit d.treuen Blick, Side A; Grub and Kub Veronika, Side B
    - Die kleinen Madchen mit dem treuen Blick, waxman_0576; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Die kleinen Madchen mit dem treuen Blick, Side A; Grub and Kub Veronika, Side B
    - Die Mainacht, waxman_0383; commercial, 78rpm; voice and piano; (recorded in Europe); Shellac disc
      Die Mainacht, side A; Der Nussbaum, side B
    - Die Meistersinger - Prelude To Act 3, waxman_0600; Shellac disc
    - Die Meistersinger Overture, waxman_0376; Shellac disc
      Die Meistersinger Overture (Part 1), Side A ;Die Meistersinger Overture (Concluded), Side B
    - Die Natali, recorded 12/23/1960; waxman_0784; orchestral performance recording; Lacquer discs/acetates
      Die Natalie, side A
    - Digital Premiere Recordings from the Films of Alfred Hitchcock: Family Plot - Strangers On A Train - Suspicion - Notorious, 1985; waxman_0723; Recordings from the Films of Alfred Hitchcock: Family Plot, Strangers On a Train, Suspicion, Notorious by John Williams, Dimitri Tiomkin, Franz Waxman, and Roy Webb; VinylDisc
      Side One 1. Family Plot Williams 3:54 End Credits; 2. Strangers On A Train Tiomkin 16:13 Main Title and Approaching The Train, Ann and Guy, The Warning and Bruno's Threat, The Tennis Game The Cigarette Lighter, Bruno's Death and Finale; Side Two 1. Suspicion Waxman 12:04 Main Title, Sunday Morning, The Chairs Are Back, Melbeck's Office, Looking for Johnny, Too Fast, Finale; 2. Notorious Webb Arranged and Orchestrated by C Palmer 5:46 Main Title; Unica; Troubled Mind; Alicia Collapses; Finale and End Cast
    - Digital Premiere Recordings from the Films of Alfred Hitchcock: Family Plot - Strangers On A Train - Suspicion - Notorious, 1985; waxman_0724; Recordings from the Films of Alfred Hitchcock: Family Plot, Strangers On a Train, Suspicion, Notorious by John Williams, Dimitri Tiomkin, Franz Waxman, and Roy Webb; VinylDisc